American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  June 1-4, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  June 7-10, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  June 11-20, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  June 21-30, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  July 1-12, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  July 13-21, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  July 22-30, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  August 1-9, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  August 10-13, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  August 16-20, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  August 23-31, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  September 1-8, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  September 9-11, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  September 13-17, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  September 18-23, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  September 24-27, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  September 28-30, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  October 1-4, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  October 5-7, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  October 8-12, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  October 13-18, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  October 19-20, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  October 21-24, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  October 25-28, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  October 29-31, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  November 1-3, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  November 4-5, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  November 6-11, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  November 12-15, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  November 16-18, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  November 19-22, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  November 23-26, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  November 27-30, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  December 1-6, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  December 7-9, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  December 10-11, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  December 13-14, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  December 15-16, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  December 17-20, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  December 21-24, 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  December 26-31, 1937 and undated December 1937
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 45, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  January 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  February 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  March 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  April 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  May 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  June 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  July 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  August 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  September 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  October 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  November 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  December 1938
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  January 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  February 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  March 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  April 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  May 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  June 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  July 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  August 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  September 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  October 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  November 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  December 1939
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  January 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  February 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  March 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  April 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  May 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  July 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 56)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 58)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 59)
- July 1940 (Box 47, Folder 60)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 61)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 62)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 63)
  August 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 64)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 65)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 67)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 68)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 69)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 70)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 71)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 72)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 73)
  September 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 74)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 75)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 76)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 77)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 78)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 79)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 80)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 81)
  October 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 82)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 83)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 84)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 85)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 86)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 87)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 88)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 89)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 90)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 91)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 92)
  November 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 93)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 94)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 95)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 96)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 97)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 98)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 99)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 100)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 101)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 102)
  December 1940
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 103)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 104)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 105)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 106)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 107)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 108)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 109)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 110)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 111)
- Correspondence, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 112)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 113)
  January 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 114)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 115)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 116)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 117)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  February 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  March 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  April 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  May 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  June 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  July 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  August 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  August-September 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  September 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  October 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  November 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  December 1941
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  Undated 1941
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  January 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  February 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  March 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 51)
  April 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 54)
  May 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 56)
  June 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 58)
  June-July 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 59)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 60)
  July 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 61)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 62)
  August 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 63)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 64)
  September 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 65)
  October 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 67)
  November 1942
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 68)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 69)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 70)
  December 1942
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 71)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 72)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 73)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 74)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 75)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 76)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 77)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 78)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 79)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 80)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 81)
- Undated Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 82)
- Undated Correspondence - Fragments (Box 48, Folder 83)
- Undated Correspondence - Fragments (Box 48, Folder 84)
- Organizational Material, 1906-1908 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Organizational Material, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  Jan, Feb. April
- Organizational Material, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  May, June, July, Oct.
- Organizational Material, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  Nov, Dec., ND
- Organizational Material, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  Sept., Nov.
- Organizational Material, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  Feb, March, June, July
- Organizational Material, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  Dec. ND
- Organizational Material, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Organizational Material, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Organizational Material, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Organizational Material, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Organizational Material, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Organizational Material, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Organizational Material, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Organizational Material, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Organizational Material, 1914 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Organizational Material, 1915 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Organizational Material, 1915 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Organizational Material, 1915 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Organizational Material, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Organizational Material, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Organizational Material, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  ND
- Organizational Material, 1917 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  Jan., Feb. March, May
- Organizational Material, 1917 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Organizational Material, 1918 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  Whole year
- Organizational Material, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  Jan. - August
- Organizational Material, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  Oct. - Dec. ND
- Organizational Material, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  Jan. - June
- Organizational Material, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  Sept. - Nov.
- Organizational Material, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  Dec.
- Organizational Material, 1920 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Organizational Material, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  Jan. - Nov.
- Organizational Material, 1921 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Organizational Material, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Organizational Material, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Organizational Material, 1924 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Organizational Material, 1925-1928 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Organizational Material, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Organizational Material, 1930 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Organizational Material, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  Jan. - May
- Organizational Material, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- Organizational Material, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  Jan. - April
- Organizational Material, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  May, June 1932
- Organizational Material, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  Nov, Dec. ND
- Organizational Material, 1933 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Organizational Material, 1933 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  May - October
- Organizational Material, 1933 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  Nov. Dec. ND
- Organizational Material, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  Jan. - March, Oct.
- Organizational Material, 1934 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  Nov. Dec. - ND
- Organizational Material, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Organizational Material, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 51)
- Organizational Material, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 52)
- Organizational Material, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 53)
- Organizational Material, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 54)
- Organizational Material, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 55)
- Organizational Material, 1940-1941 (Box 49, Folder 56)
- Organizational Material, 1942 (Box 49, Folder 57)
- Organizational Material, 1942 (Box 49, Folder 58)
- Organizational Material (Box 49, Folder 59)
- Organizational Material (Box 49, Folder 60)
- Organizational Material (Box 49, Folder 61)
- Organizational Material (Box 49, Folder 62)
- Organizational Material (Box 49, Folder 63)
- Organizational Material (Box 49, Folder 64)
- Organizational Material Fragmentary Material (Box 49, Folder 65)
- General Labor Laws, 1909-1918 (Box 49, Folder 66)
- General Labor Law, 1909-1918 (Box 49, Folder 67)
- General Labor Law, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 68)
- General Labor Law, 1920-1925 (Box 49, Folder 69)
- General Labor Law, 1926-1930 (Box 49, Folder 70)
- General Labor Law, 1931-1932 (Box 49, Folder 71)
- General Labor Law, 1935-1943 (Box 49, Folder 72)
- General Labor Law - Undated (Box 49, Folder 73)
- General Social Insurance (Box 50, Folder 1)
  No date. 1 of 3.
- General Social Insurance (Box 50, Folder 2)
  No date. 2 of 3.
- General Social Insurance (Box 50, Folder 3)
  No date. 3 of 3.
- Social Insurance (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Social Insurance (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Social Insurance (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Social Insurance (Box 50, Folder 7)
- General Social Insurance, 1909-1912 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- General Social Insurance, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- General Social Insurance, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- General Social Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  1 of 4
- General Social Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  2 of 4
- General Social Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  3 of 4
- General Social Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  4 of 4
- General Social Insurance, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  February, August, September 1917
- General Social Insurance, 1917-1918 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  October and undated 1917; 1918
- General Social Insurance, 1919-1930 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  1919, 1921, 1926, 1927, 1930
- General Social Insurance, 1933-1935 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- General Social Insurance, 1936-1937 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Health Insurance, 1911-1912 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Health Insurance, 1913 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Health Insurance, 1913 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Health Insurance, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  May-June 1914
- Health Insurance, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  September, October, and December 1914
- Health Insurance, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  Undated 1914. 1 of 4.
- Health Insurance, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  Undated 1914. 2 of 4.
- Health Insurance, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  Undated 1914. 3 of 4.
- Health Insurance, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  Undated 1914. 4 of 4.
- Health Insurance, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  February, August-October 1915
- Health Insurance, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  November 1915
- Health Insurance, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  November-December 1915
- Health Insurance, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  Undated 1915. 1 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  Undated 1915. 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  Undated 1915. 3 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  January 1916. 1 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  January 1916. 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  January 1916. 3 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  February 1916
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  March 1916. 1 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  March 1916. 2 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  April-May 1916
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  May 1916.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  June-August 1916
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  September 1916. 1 of 3
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  September 1916. 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  September 1916. 3 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 47)
  October 1916.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  November 1916. 1 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  November 1916. 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  November 1916. 3 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  December 1916.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  Undated 1916. 1 of 7.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  Undated 1916. 2 of 7.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  Undated 1916. 3 of 7.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 55)
  Undated 1916. 4 of 7.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 56)
  Undated 1916. 5 of 7
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 57)
  Undated 1916. 6 of 7.
- Health Insurance, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 58)
  Undated 1916. 7 of 7.
- Health Insurance, 1920 (Box 50, Folder 59)
  January and March 1920
- Health Insurance, 1920 (Box 50, Folder 60)
  April-May and August 1920
- Health Insurance, 1921-1930 (Box 50, Folder 61)
  1921-1923, 1930
- Health Insurance, 1932-1933 (Box 50, Folder 62)
  1932-1933
- Health Insurance, 1934-1940 (Box 50, Folder 63)
  1934, 1936, 1938-1940
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 64)
  No date. File 1.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 65)
  No date. File 2.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 66)
  No date. File 3.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 67)
  No date. File 4.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 68)
  No date. File 5.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 69)
  No date. File 6.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 70)
  No date. File 7.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 71)
  No date. File 8.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 72)
  No date. File 9.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 73)
  No date. File 10.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 74)
  No date. File 11.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 75)
  No date. File 12.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 76)
  No date. File 13.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 77)
  No date. File 14.
- Health Insurance (Box 50, Folder 78)
  No date. File 15.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  January 1917. 1 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  January 1917. 2 of 2.